[
  {
    "question": "Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when ",
    "variants": ["Right", "Wrong", "Wrong", "Wrong"],
    "answer": [0],
    "prize": 500
  },
  {
    "question": "question 2",
    "variants": ["Wrong", "Right", "Wrong", "Right"],
    "answer": [1, 3],
    "prize": 1000
  },
  {
    "question": "question 3",
    "variants": ["Right", "Wrong", "Right", "Wrong"],
    "answer": [0, 2],
    "prize": 2000
  },
  {
    "question": "question 4",
    "variants": ["Wrong", "Wrong", "Wrong", "Right"],
    "answer": [3],
    "prize": 4000
  },
  {
    "question": "question 5",
    "variants": ["Right", "Wrong", "Wrong", "Wrong"],
    "answer": [0],
    "prize": 8000
  },
  {
    "question": "question 6",
    "variants": ["Wrong", "Right", "Wrong", "Wrong"],
    "answer": [1],
    "prize": 16000
  },
  {
    "question": "question 7",
    "variants": ["Wrong", "Wrong", "Right", "Wrong"],
    "answer": [2],
    "prize": 32000
  },
  {
    "question": "question 8",
    "variants": ["Wrong", "Wrong", "Wrong", "Right"],
    "answer": [3],
    "prize": 64000
  },
  {
    "question": "question 9",
    "variants": ["Right", "Wrong", "Wrong", "Wrong"],
    "answer": [0],
    "prize": 125000
  },
  {
    "question": "question 10",
    "variants": ["Wrong", "Right", "Wrong", "Wrong"],
    "answer": [1],
    "prize": 250000
  },
  {
    "question": "question 11",
    "variants": ["Wrong", "Wrong", "Right", "Wrong"],
    "answer": [2],
    "prize": 5000000
  },
  {
    "question": "question 12",
    "variants": ["Wrong", "Wrong", "Wrong", "Right"],
    "answer": [3],
    "prize": 1000000
  }
]
